Then it is about reducing the spread of infection as much as possible.
If you have a broader perspective where you take in the slightly more long -term financial health issues
So maybe you get another answer.
Therefore, it becomes very difficult to say what is right.
To that should be added that I do not think that we will even be able to say what was right, in retrospect, we will be able to say, what was right,
If Sweden chose right, so to speak, because we can never know.
If we go back and say that
Sweden had chosen Norway's strategy instead, what would it have meant?
We don't know that.
But it feels a little frustrating that we may never ever know which strategy was right.
No, but that's how it is precisely when we have this great uncertainty, that it may not be possible to say.
You have to make decisions anyway.
I would say that is the content of this with decisions under uncertainty.
You can only cook by position.
What do you think stands out with Swedish politicians' actions during the Corona crisis?
Then it is partly that the experts may do different analyzes of the same knowledge
But also that you have completely different conditions in different countries.
It sounds like this is rational, now we will find some good strategy to fight the spread of infection.
But are there not completely different reasons why politicians make decisions?
Don't they just want to show action too?
You have to make a decision to show that you are doing something?
Well, it is clear, to a large extent it is.
Then I would not say that it is not rational.
It is not easy to draw that limit.
It again depends on the perspective you take.
If you take a broader perspective and say that a large part of this is to calm the population,
That people should feel that politicians take this seriously, that they do something,
That they do not care when people get sick, die and become unemployed.
It is a very important part of politics.
So that with action is rational